[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING IN PAIN]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECH]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[TRUCK HORN BLARES]
[LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- Stop!
- [GUNSHOTS]
Don't!
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
[METAL RODS CLANGING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [BUS HORN HONKS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [TRUCK HORN HONKS]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOT]
- [BODY THUDS]
- [GUNSHOT]
Why did he kiss you?!
Bring his ass to me!
I'll beat him up!
- I won't spare him!
- I told you, enough!
I'm the one who got wronged.
I'll deal with it.
Once I find out who he is,
I'll throw him in jail myself!
I'm back where I belong.
- It's Gabo!
It's Gabo! It's Gabo!
[SMOOCHING]
Gabo, I've missed you!
Why didn't you tell me
you were going home?
- Tekla?
- Yes, it's me!
- Pa! Pa!
- Gabo!
It's Gabo! He's here!
It's Gabo. We saw him here.
He's out.
He went home.
Tell him to meet me
at the headquarters.
Hey, Gabo!
Django is asking for you.
If he wants revenge,
we'll settle it here.
Will you prove to us that
you have changed your ways now?
I'm going to bet my life on it.
My son is turning
over a new leaf.
- [DOOR CRASHES]
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Where's Django?!
- Where is he?!
- [BLADE SWISHES]
Where's Django?!
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[BLADE SWISHES]
Where's Django?! Where is he?!
- Django!
- You're dead meat!
[BETCHAY] Gabo, stop it!
Django, where are you?!
Where are you?!
Move!
Django!
[BASKET THUDS]
- [BLADE SWISHES]
- Get out of there!
Django!
- [LIQUID TRICKLING]
- Hurry up, people! Get moving!
We need to
hang those immediately!
Hurry up! Load it up.
We're in a time crunch.
Hey! Do your job quickly.
Clock is ticking.
Why are these not organized?
Clean it up.
Hurry up.
- Gabo, stop it!
- Don't go in!
I'll go in alone! Stay here!
- [BLADE SWISHES]
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
Gabo!
Rudy! Gabo might get killed!
Don't go in!
He can handle this alone!
Let him be!
Django!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Welcome back, Gabo.
You guys can take care of that!
- [BLADE SWISHING]
- [PEOPLE SCREAMING]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [BODY THUDS]
[BLADE SWISHING]
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [BODY THUDS]
[BLADE SWISHING]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [BODY THUDS]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
Oh god!
- [KICKS LANDING]
- [BODIES THUDDING]
[KICK LANDS]
- [BODY THUDS]
- [LOUD THUD]
[BLADE SWISHING]
- [KICKS LAND]
- [HEAD BANGS]
Aah!
[BLADE SWISHES]
- [SCREAMING]
- [BODIES THUDDING]
[BLADE SWISHING]
[BODY THUDS]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [BODY THUDS]
[BLADES SWISHING]
- [KICKS LAND]
- [BODIES THUD]
- [BLADE SWISHING]
- [MAN GRUNTING]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [BODY THUDS]
[BLADE SWISHING]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [BODY THUDS]
[BLADES SWISHING]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [BODY THUDS]
- [BLADES SWISHING]
- [GABO GRUNTING]
[KICK LANDS]
- [BODY THUDS]
- [BLADE CLANKS]
- Django!
- Come on, Django!
Rudy, let's go inside
before Gabo gets beaten up!
Are you nuts?! We already
told you not to!
We told you not to!
Rudy, let's head in!
Come on!
- Stay here!
- Rudy!
- Wait!
Gabo!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
[THUDS]
[BLOWS LANDING]
- [INHALES SHARPLY]
- [BOTH GROANING]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[WINDOWS SHATTERING]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
[THUDDING]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GRUNTING IN PAIN]
[KICK LANDS]
[CRASHES]
- Where's Gabo?!
- Move!
- What? Huh?!
- [SMACKS]
- Where is Gabo?!
- Where is he?! Huh?!
- Where's Gabo?!
- [HIT LANDS]
- [GRUNTS IN PAIN]
[BLOWS LANDING]
- [CHAINS CLINKING]
- Where is he?!
- He's over there!
- Sit down!
- [HITS LANDING]
- Gabo!
Let's move!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GABO] You bastard!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
You bastard.
You thought I was gonna
forget about it?
I got imprisoned for eight years
because of you!
You'll pay for all of it!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GABO GRUNTING]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [THUDDING]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [RUDY] Gabo!
- [BONG] Gabo!
- Gabo, stop!
- Gabo, that's enough.
[PEOPLE CLAMORING IN DISTANCE]
Serves him right.
He'll learn his lesson for sure.
He'll never be able to show his
face here in Ginintuang Lupa.
Because you'll be reigning
these parts from now on.
We should leave immediately
before Sir Paquito gets here!
- [ELTON] Let's go, Rudy!
- Come on!
Let's leave!
- Let's go, Gabo!
- Come on, Gabo!
[RUDY] Gabo! Gabo!
- [RUDY] Gabo!
- It's Gabo!
It's Gabo!
Shame on you, Gabo!
You ruined our neighborhood!
You ruined our livelihood!
You'll pay for this!
[RUDY] Gabo!
[IBYANG] Scram!
I'll make sure Paquito
knows of this!
[MOCKINGLY] Ooh, scary.
Come on. Let's head inside.
We have to help them!
How are we gonna get in when
they have all those weapons?!
Why'd you bring a rusty pot?!
What can you do with that?!
- Dante, go inside.
- Enough, both of you!
Dante, you have to go inside.
Get in now!
Why me?! What if I die
in there?!
- What?!
- You two head in then!
You bastard,
why should we go first?!
Get in there before I kill you.
- I'll kill you myself!
- Alright, alright!
- [MAMENG] Oh!
- [DANTE] Oh, Gabo!
- [BETCHAY] Gabo!
- Gabo, what happened?!
Where's your father?!
Where's Rudy?!
Rudy!
- Hey, Rudy...
- Oh!
- What happened?
- [DANTE] What happened?
[BONG] It's over.
Because Django was beaten
to a pulp by Gabo!
That means, Gabo is the new king
of Ginintuang Lupa!
- Long live Gabo!
- [ALL] Long live!
- To the new king!
- [ALL] To the new king!
- All hail Gabo!
- All hail!
[BONG] Long li--
- Huh?
- Gabo!
Gabo! Gabo!
[PEOPLE CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
[BETCHAY] I knew it.
[BETCHAY] I already told you!
Gabo!
- [CRASHES, RATTLES]
- [WOMAN 1] Oh!
- [WOMAN 1] Oh my gosh!
- [WOMAN 2] Ah!
- [WOMAN 2] Oh!
- [WIRE GATE RATTLES]
- [INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
What are you all looking at?
- What are you all looking at?!
- [PEOPLE SCREAM]
- Django!
- [BINOY] Django!
Cowards!
Boss!
Get your hands off of me!
[THUDS]
- Sorry, boss.
- You too!
- [TOLITS] Go and help him!
- You do it!
- [CRASHES]
- Bunch of cowards!
[DJANGO BREATHING HEAVILY]
- [CRASHES]
- [BOTH GRUNT]
- [SCREAMING]
- [IBYANG] Django!
[OBJECTS CRASHING, THUDDING]
Django!
- [WATER SPLASHING]
- [DJANGO GRUNTING]
[SCREAMING]
This won't be the last
you'll see me, Gabo.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Once I see you again,
I'll send you to your grave.
I'll send you to your grave!
- [SMACKS]
- [DJANGO GRUNTS]
- Django!
- [DJANGO SCREAMS]
[STUTTERING] D-Django,
are you o-okay?
Are you okay?
Django, you good?
- [KICK LANDS]
- [ALL SCREAM]
He's good! More than good!
- [BINOY] Django!
- Django!
- Django, calm down!
- We're on your side!
[IBYANG] That's enough!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Gabo!
[RUDY] Gabo!
Hey, Gabo!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Gabo!
- What's your problem?!
- [BETCHAY] Rudy!
[RUDY] Gabo!
Didn't we just talk about this?!
You promised you'd change
for the better!
But that animal's gone too far!
I just got out of jail
and he's already provoking me!
He's the reason I was jailed
in the first place!
Well, too bad for him!
Now everyone knows who's boss
here in Ginintuang Lupa!
- Yeah.
- He's right.
[DANTE] Gabo.
You really can't control
your anger, can you?
What if Paquito
gets back at you?
[IPE] Oh, I don't think so.
Gabo crushed all his enemies.
[BONG] You saw, didn't you?
He beat all of them to a pulp.
I doubt they'd want another go.
They're probably too embarrassed
to show up here again.
I'm sure after this, no one will
follow them out of fear again.
- Yeah!
- That's right!
That's where you're wrong.
I know Paquito.
He'll just find another way
to torment us again.
Let them try, Miss Mameng!
They'll get more than a beating
from Gabo.
[DIDAY] Gabo!
If Django and Paquito
return here for revenge,
we'll back you up!
- Right, everyone?!
- [WEAKLY] Y-Yes.
Louder!
Or I'll hit you in the face!
- Yeah!
- We got your back!
- You can count on us!
[RUDY] Gabo.
It's only your first day
out of jail,
but you already put
our family at risk!
Now, we'll have to live
in constant fear,
dreading the day Paquito's group
returns for payback.
Just let them try!
If they lay a finger on you,
I'll fight back even if it means
ending up in jail again!
[MUSIC TURNS MOROSE]
What are you looking at,
you nosybodies?!
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [PUNCHING BAG CHAINS RATTLE]
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[BETCHAY]
What did I tell you?
He hasn't changed at all.
Come on, Rudy.
He's been getting into fights
ever since he was a kid.
He's been into all kinds
of trouble!
[MAMENG]
Hey, watch your mouth.
What did Gabo ever do to you?
Why do you always think
the worst of him?
Is it because he's not
your real son?
- Wait a minute--
- Is that why...
...you never gave him
your support?
Hey! How dare you say
I never supported that kid?!
I raised him!
I stood up as his mother!
I'm just saying the truth
because I know him.
I know Gabo damn well!
- That's enough now,
- So you have no right...
- ...to question me!
- Miss Betchay, that's enough.
We all know the truth, okay?
We know Gabo is a good guy.
Unless he's provoked, of course.
Because then he'd retaliate.
- I didn't--
- Enough! That's enough!
Enough.
I'll talk to Gabo.
I haven't given up hope
that he'll change.
Just let me talk to him.
[BETCHA] Rudy!
- This is all your fault.
- Why me? You started this.
- Me?
- Enough.
- You're spewing nonsense!
- I'm just saying the truth!
- Okay, that's enough! Enough!
- Calm down. Stop it!
[RUDY] Gabo.
Why did you do that?!
Tell me!
You promised you'd change
for the better, didn't you?!
What if something bad
had happened to you?!
What if they killed you?!
But they've gone too far, Pa!
Django has gone too far!
Ever since I was a kid...
he has always picked on me.
He has been tormenting me.
He's the reason I was imprisoned
for eight years!
So, while I was behind bars,
I promised myself
that when I get out,
I'll make him feel all
the suffering I went through!
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
Son...
Don't waste your life.
You're still young.
Don't waste your time
getting revenge from
those good-for-nothing pricks!
I have so many dreams for you.
But most of all, I just want you
to have a good life.
That's all I want.
Son, I'm your father.
[SNIFFLES] Do you love me
as your father?
[SIGHS DEEPLY]
I love you, Pa.
Please forgive me.
I'm sorry I got carried away.
Son...
if you really love me,
please listen
to what I'm telling you.
I just want you to live
a decent life.
I... I just want you...
to have a good family.
I want you to have
a better future.
To get you out of this place.
[RUDY SOBBING SOFTLY]
I understand you.
Please forgive me
for what I did earlier.
For letting my emotions
get the best of me.
And for what I did to Django.
Son, if you love me...
please take my words to heart.
I won't make you do anything
that will ruin your life.
Now that you're free...
please don't go back
to your old ways.
Pa...
I love you very much.
And I have so much
respect for you.
I promise you...
that starting tomorrow...
I'll try my best to change.
I'll look for a job.
And I'll avoid getting
into any trouble.
[RUDY SNIFFLING]
Thank you, son.
- Thank you.
- I'm sorry, Pa.
- [RUDY SNIFFLES]
- Please forgive me.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
Update me on the surveillance
in Chinatown, okay?
- Yes, ma'am.
Alright, I'll get going.
- I'll come along.
- Come on.
Uh... Sam, Sam! Hold on.
You left something.
Here.
You left these.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
You forgot these.
That's for the most beautiful
woman here in NCIA.
Not for her desk.
Oh, are you headed home?
Let me escort you so I know
you'll get home safely.
No need. I can protect myself.
Is that so?
Just text me then.
Bye.
Take care, Sam.
Put those in a vase.
They're pretty.
[PLAYFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KAREN EXHALES]
Your future boyfriend
is so sweet.
Excuse me.
He's not my future boyfriend.
Why not?
Did you see
how he acted earlier?
He acts as if
we're in a relationship.
He even wanted me to text him.
[SCOFFS] Who the hell is he?
He's Sir Sebastian.
The one.
Whatever. I'm going home.
Karen! Karen! Hold on.
Do you think Sir Seb
has a chance with Ma'am Sam?
That's the thing.
Looks like her heart
needs to defrost for a while.
Well then, we'll make it work.
I know they'll end up together.
- True.
- But if they can't be together
then...
I think we can be together.
Ugh!
Don't say that again.
[QUIRKY MUSIC PLAYING]
Such nonsense.
[QUIRKY MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC FADES]
He's so full of himself.
He just came back...
and he thinks
he runs Ginintuang Lupa.
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What's your plan, Django?
I'll let him enjoy his win
right now.
[CHUCKLES EVILLY]
But when the time comes,
I'll make sure...
he never gets up.
You're right, boss.
We have to make Gabo pay.
Sooner or later, boss,
we have to make him pay.
[TOLITS]
You guys know Django well.
- He doesn't accept defeat.
- Take a shot, man!
He'll sure get back at Gabo.
The problem will get worse
if this reaches Paquito.
Those two will make Gabo's life
a living hell
until they get even.
Not only to Gabo.
The whole Ginintuang Lupa will
be in chaos if that happens.
Hold, on, hold on, hold on.
Ouch!
- Sorry, sorry.
- What is it?
What if...
we just abandon the group?
I don't want to work
for that father and son anymore.
What do you think?
[PLAYFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
You're right.
Let's dip out.
- We'll start a new group.
- [EXCLAIMS]
Shhh!
So we won't have any cuts
from our earnings.
We won't have to give anything
to Paquito and Django.
- Right? Right?
- That's true! That's true!
Hold on, hold on. If we dip out,
Django and Paquito
might get back at us.
You're a coward, aren't you
Are you a coward?
Then...
- We'll befriend Gabo.
- Oh, yes.
- Huh?
- If we're friends with Gabo,
for sure, we'll have protection.
- Yes.
- You saw what happened earlier.
- Gabo knocked out Django.
- Yes.
- You saw it. You too.
You saw it, right?
That's what I'm saying.
If we side with Gabo,
we'll get caught in their fight.
You backing down already, huh?
Are you that unsure?
What's your problem, huh?
No matter what we do,
those two will clash again.
What matters is backing
whoever's got the upper hand.
- And we just saw Gabo!
- Oh!
- Gabo! You get it now?
- Exactly.
So do we have a plan?
- Alright? Our plan's set.
- I'm good with it.
- Gabo.
- You can handle this, yeah?
- Suit yourselves.
- Come on, let's go.
We're with Gabo,
he's the strong one.
You saw what happened
to Django, right?
Turns out he's all bark,
no bite.
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
- Good evening, ma'am!
- Good evening.
Thank you.
Mac, open the big gate,
will you?
- It's risky bringing out the...
- [KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Sam?
- Sam. Dear.
- Mom.
What happened to you?
Did you get hurt?
- No. I'm okay, Mom.
- Huh? Are you sure?
Wow,
you were incredible out there!
And your mom and I
watched the whole thing!
Honestly, it was so impressive!
You've really got
something special, ma'am!
- [ISOBEL] Exactly.
- Go! Go, Sam! You were amazing!
You really are something else.
I know she's always good
at doing her job,
so I never doubted
you'd be safe.
Hmm!
- Dear, where did these...
- Ay, oo nga! Oh my gosh!
...beautiful flowers come from?
- They're so heavy.
- They're from Sebastian.
The guy who's been
courting you forever?
Look at that. So sweet!
So, are you finally
going to say yes?
Mom, I'm not thinking
about that right now.
Oh, is that so?
Yes, Mom.
That's not our priority.
Our careers come first.
In fact, here's the proof.
You brought work home.
No.
There's an explanation for this.
I need to finish
our investigation.
Sir Delgado just
made me team leader.
Really?!
- Mm! [CHUCKLES]
- I'm so proud of you, dear.
Your dad would be too.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
Speaking of your dad,
he has something
important to tell both of you.
That's why Aunt Pinky's here.
- Let's go.
- Come on.
- Man, I'm dying of thirst.
- Okay.
Come on, hurry.
- Okay, Pinky, look who's here.
- Oh, hi!
Hello!
- Go say hi.
- Oh, hello! [SMOOCHES]
Hi, Aunt Pinky!
- I missed you.
- It's nice you could stop by.
Yes!
What's up?
Well, your Aunt Pinky has this
piece of property she's selling.
Your mom and I thought it was
a great business opportunity,
so we bought it.
With the economy so unstable,
high oil prices,
conflicts everywhere,
and endless corruption
here in the Philippines,
the previous owner
decided to move abroad.
So we got the land
for a really low price.
- Where's this property located?
- In Ginintuang Lupa.
Investors are already
interested.
They would like to see the
property next week.
Yes, it's a very,
very good location.
The mayor has big plans
for that area.
And Isobel, if this goes
through? We'll be
sitting on a goldmine.
Yes.
Wait a second, Ginintuang Lupa?
But there are so many families
living there.
And that area's known for crime.
There's nothing
to worry about, Sam.
The court already
ordered them to leave.
They should've been gone
ages ago.
But Max,
where are they supposed to go?
Sam.
Don't worry about
where they'll end up.
They'll just move
to the hills or somewhere.
They always find
a place to stay.
They're used to fending
for themselves.
But, Mom, we can't just
let them be.
Many families
will be left homeless.
Let's put it this way.
They've been staying at
Ginintuang Lupa for years.
So, as the new owners,
it's our turn to make use
of that property. Okay?
That's my decision
and that's final.
Okay.
So, have you signed it?
- Yes, I did.
- It's all done?
Oh, there's something
I'd like to discuss with you.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
- Knock, knock.
- Oh. Hi.
How's my team leader?
Hmm?
Well...
I brought you some coffee
to boost your energy.
- Thank you.
- I'm going to bed too.
- Alright.
- Max.
I want to ask you something.
What?
Do you really agree
with Daddy's decision?
Well...
Yeah.
That's a good investment.
Don't you think?
I'm just worried about those
people who'll lose their homes.
There are many
families there.
Shouldn't we protect them
as enforcers of the law?
No. No, Sam.
Remember, they are
illegal settlers.
It is our
job to enforce the law.
Okay?
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
I wonder what RJ would
say about all of this.
What would he say?
He'd always agree to what
Daddy says.
He'd go, "Yes, okay."
Enough of the drama, okay?
Stop thinking negative thoughts.
I mean, come on.
Look at your achievements.
You're a team leader,
and you were a hero
during that bus incident.
Oh come on, Max.
Don't mention that bus
incident again.
It's making my blood boil.
Why? What happened?
A guy took advantage
of me.
What?!
What exactly did he do?
He kissed me.
He kissed you?! Does he know
that's harassment?
I'll file charges
against him.
I'll arrest him myself.
Where is he?
I don't even know
his name.
What does he look like?
Describe him to me.
["TUNAY NA LIGAYA"
BY JUAN KARLOS PLAYING]
Why are you smiling?
- I was smiling?
- Yes.
What are you talking about?
I wasn't smiling.
Yes, I saw it.
What? That's gross.
Why would I smile?
Did you find what he did
offensive?
Yes, of course.
Besides, if you've seen
what he looks like,
you'll see that he's
gross and filthy.
He looks unkempt and in
need of a shower.
Plus, his hair looks dry.
And no one in their right mind
would pretend to faint
and kiss a stranger.
No decent guy would do that
unless he's a pervert.
That was such a long answer
for one question.
I thought you were going
to bed.
Go. Go to bed, okay?
- Okay, fine.
- Good night.
Are you going to think of him
while trying to sleep?
- Stop it. Good night!
- Good night!
["TUNAY NA LIGAYA" CONTINUES]
[RUDY] Yes, Gabo and I talked.
He promised
he'd turn over a new leaf.
[BONG] Wow.
Is that true, Gabo?
A while ago, you said
you were going to behave.
You went inside, you came
back out, and attacked Django.
[LAUGHTER]
[IPE] C'mon, Gabo,
we know you very well,
so I am sure
that will never happen!
You guys are
so hard on Gabo!
Why don't we try
trusting our friend?
Who knows, maybe this time
it's for real, right?
- We really hope so.
- [CHUCKLING]
- It's real this time.
I already promised Papa.
I told him that...
I'm really going
to turn over a new leaf.
I've been thinking...
I spent a long time in prison,
and if I just waste my life,
nothing will come of it.
Do you believe me now?
- [BETCHAY] Hmm.
- Alright.
- Take a shot.
- Your father is right, Gabo.
- [COUGHS]
- Don't stoop to their level.
Their lives are already
ruined anyway,
that's why they do things
that harm others.
[MAMENG] And don't let your
temper get the better of you.
It might just end up ruining
your life and your future.
Those people are just looking
for someone
to drag down with them.
[IPE] They're back Gabo.
To be honest, you don't
have to prove them anything.
Everyone around here knows
that Django is no match for you
That's why he wants
to get back at you, right?
Yeah, but the problem is
when they both get involved...
- I'll get mad.
- [LAUGHTER]
Oh, Rudy, your son?
He won't be able to hold back!
He's always looking for a fight!
As soon as he gets
out in the streets...
- kapow!
- [LAUGHTER]
Don't encourage him!
- Enough.
- [MAMENG] Wait a minute!
Why are you always
against Gabo?
- You started it!
- Let's cheers to that.
- [LAUGHTER]
- [TEKLA] Stop it.
Aunt Betchay.
In my conversation
with my father,
I really told him
that I'm turning over
a new leaf,
so tomorrow...
I'll look for a job.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
Hey, man.
- Hey.
- Do you repair motorcycles?
Yes, we do!
Do you need yours fixed?
Yes, the side of my motorcycle
got damaged.
Bring it here tomorrow
so we can see it.
How much do you think
it will cost?
- Just the sides, right?
- Yes, just the sides.
It might be around two thousand.
[BETCHAY] He'll look for a job!
Really? Thank goodness
you won't go around
fighting anymore!
[CHUCKLING]
Hey, you guys.
If you want,
you can join me in looking
for a job tomorrow
- Sure!
- Yeah!
We'll definitely go
with you to earn money.
- We're your plus ones!
- [TEKLA] You're right.
Hey, this is perfect!
We're actually being kicked
out of the house.
They even had the nerve
to call us useless.
[LAUGHTER]
[RUDY] You should tell them
that they're right!
[TEKLA] That's right. Cheers!
- [LAUGHTER]
- They're right!
I was just joking! C'mon!
Someone's interested in
the motorcycle you're fixing.
He wants to buy it.
What? But it's not for sale.
Yeah, but... why don't you
talk to him instead?
- [MAMENG] Who is it?
- Wait a minute.
- Who is it?
- He's buying it?
- Hey, grab a drink with us!
- Take a shot with us!
I can't it's against
my religion.
[BONG] His religion? What is it?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
This is Rudy, he assembles
all the motorcycles here.
Is that customized, sir?
[ELTON] It is. He assembled it
on his own.
The owner of it is a seaman.
He just hasn't gone back to it.
Is that so? How much do those
usually cost, sir?
[RUDY] Oh, it usually could go
up to 300,000 pesos.
It's quite expensive, huh.
- It's as expensive as a car.
- But well, look at it!
- It's real sleek.
- Mm-hmm. It's stunning.
[RUDY] You can consider it
as an artwork.
[ELTON] Its wheels alone
is already gorgeous.
[RUDY] Mm-hmm.
[ELTON] It already looks good.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Well then, sir.
- I'll come back tomorrow.
- Sure. We'll wait for you.
[RUDY] You should customize
yours, too!
[ELTON] Yeah.
- [MAMENG LAUGHING]
- [TEKLA] Oh, dear...
- [IPE] There he goes.
- [MAMENG WHEEZING, COUGHS]
[MAMENG] What? Did they strike
a deal?
[BONG] Gabo!
- [BONG] You good?
- [MAMENG] Are you alright?
That man was glaring at me.
Why? Who was it?
I recognize his face but I can't
remember who he is.
Maybe he offended you before!
- That bastard!
- Hey! Hey! Hey!
- Hold it!
- Stop right there! Hey!
Hey! What's up with him?
Who's he after?
I thought he'll change but now
he's causing trouble again!
Why would they go after him
he's just buying a motorcycle?
[BONG] Hey!
Hey!
Come on. Let's go to Gabo!
- [BONG] Gabo!
- [TEKLA] Oh, they're here.
We couldn't catch him.
- Why?
- He's quite quick.
I thought you said
he's just a turtle to you.
- Man, was he quick.
- [LAUGHTER]
Turns out you were the turtles!
- So it were you guys.
Stop standing around
and clean this up!
- Come on, let's tidy up.
- You frauds!
- I got it.
- This one's not finished yet.
[ELTON] Alright, pack it up!
- [RUDY] Go home already!
- [ELTON] I'll go home now.
- [BONG] Come on.
- [RUDY] You should get going.
- [BONG] Bye, Sir Rudy!
- [RUDY] Be careful!
- [BONG] Thanks, Gabo!
- [RUDY] Yeah!
[TEKLA] Good night!
- I'll get going. Take care.
- See you tomorrow!
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
[WATER SPLASHES]
[ELECTRIC BUZZING]
[SCREAMING IN PAIN]
[GABO SCREAMING, GROANING
IN PAIN]
I do hope you really change
for the better.
Don't worry, Pa. I'll see to it
that once we come back here,
we already have jobs.
Your son, Gabo, is really kind.
He's just really unfortunate.
Get yours now!
What? We look like thugs?
Come here yourself then!
I don't think these punks
know who we are!
You're brave hiding behind
your screens, huh?!
[CRASHES]
[MALE VO] Whoever goes against
the people of Ginintuang Lupa...
I own this land!
[MALE VO] is sure to fall.
Ricardo!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [BOTH GRUNTING]
[THUDS]
[PEOPLE CLAMORING]
[MALE VO] It's time to show off
this Thursday.
[MALE VO] Coco Martin's Sigabo.